<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet href="/externalflash/NASA_Detail/NASA_Detail.xsl" type="text/xsl"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<!-- ORIGIN: http://www.nasa.gov/rss/breaking_news.rss -->
	<channel>
		<title>NASA Breaking News</title>
		<link>http://www.nasa.gov/audience/formedia/features/index.html</link>
		<description>A RSS news feed containing the latest NASA news articles and press releases.</description>
		<language>en-us</language>
		<docs>http://blogs.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<managingEditor>jim.wilson@nasa.gov</managingEditor>
		<webMaster>brian.dunbar@nasa.gov</webMaster>
		<item>
			<title>NASA'S Curiosity Rover Provides Clues to Changes in Martian Atmosphere</title>
			<link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_12-387_Mars_Atmosphere.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_12-387_Mars_Atmosphere.html</guid>
			<description>NASA's car-sized rover, Curiosity, has taken significant steps toward understanding how Mars may have lost much of its original atmosphere.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Spot The Space Station Over Your Backyard With New NASA Service</title>
			<link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_12-384_Spot_Station.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_12-384_Spot_Station.html</guid>
			<description>On the 12th anniversary of crews continuously living and working aboard the International Space Station, NASA announced Friday a new service to help people see the orbiting laboratory when it passes overhead.</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 Nov 2012 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>NASA Selects Contract for Safety, Environmental, Medical Services</title>
			<link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/nov/HQ_C12-056_Ames_Safety_Contract.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/nov/HQ_C12-056_Ames_Safety_Contract.html</guid>
			<description>NASA has selected Earth Resources Technology, Inc., (ERT), of Laurel, Md., to receive a contract for safety, environmental, and medical support services at the agency's Ames Research Center, Moffett Field, Calif. The contract has a maximum value of $55 million.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>NASA Seeks Options For SLS Cargo Payload Fairings And Adapters</title>
			<link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/nov/HQ_12-386_SLS_RFI.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/nov/HQ_12-386_SLS_RFI.html</guid>
			<description>NASA is exploring options for larger payload fairings to enhance the cargo carrying capabilities of its Space Launch System (SLS) heavy-lift rocket, now in development, to carry cargo, crewed spacecraft and science payloads. In a Request for Information (RFI) published Thursday, the agency is seeking information about payload adapters and fairings already available within commercial industry.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>NASA'S Fermi Measures Cosmic 'Fog' Produced By Ancient Starlight</title>
			<link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/nov/HQ_12-385_Fermi_Fog.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/nov/HQ_12-385_Fermi_Fog.html</guid>
			<description>Astronomers using data from NASA's Fermi Gamma-ray Space Telescope have made the most accurate measurement of starlight in the universe and used it to establish the total number of stars that have ever shone, accomplishing a primary mission goal.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>SpaceX Transitions to Third Commercial Crew Phase with NASA</title>
			<link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/nov/HQ_12-378_SpaceX_Commercial_Crew_Milestones.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/nov/HQ_12-378_SpaceX_Commercial_Crew_Milestones.html</guid>
			<description>Space Exploration Technologies (SpaceX) has completed its first three performance milestones for NASA's Commercial Crew Integrated Capability (CCiCap) initiative, which is intended to lead to the availability of commercial human spaceflight services for government and commercial customers.</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Nov 2012 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>NASA Selects Contract for Architect Engineering Services</title>
			<link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_C12-058_Ames_AE_Svcs.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_C12-058_Ames_AE_Svcs.html</guid>
			<description>NASA has selected AECOM Technical Services Inc. of San Francisco, to support architect engineering services for the Facilities Engineering Branch at the agency's Ames Research Center in Moffett Field, Calif.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>NASA Awards Contract Modification for Integrated Communications Services</title>
			<link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_C12-057_GSFC_NSSC_SAIC_Mod.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_C12-057_GSFC_NSSC_SAIC_Mod.html</guid>
			<description>NASA has awarded Science Applications International Corp. (SAIC) of Mclean, Va., a modification to its integrated communications services contract at the agency's Goddard Space Flight Center in Greenbelt, Md.; Wallops Flight Facility on Wallops Island, Va.; and Goddard Institute for Space Studies in New York.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>NASA Hosts Nov. 2 Teleconference About Mars Rover Progress</title>
			<link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_M12-211_Mars_Atmosphere_Telecon.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_M12-211_Mars_Atmosphere_Telecon.html</guid>
			<description>NASA will host a media teleconference at 10 a.m. PDT (1 p.m. EDT) Friday, Nov. 2, to provide an update on Curiosity's studies of the Martian atmosphere.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>NASA-WPI 2013 Robot Prize Competition Registration Open</title>
			<link>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_12-377_NASA-WPI_2013_Robot_Competition_Registration.html</link>
			<guid>http://www.nasa.gov/home/hqnews/2012/oct/HQ_12-377_NASA-WPI_2013_Robot_Competition_Registration.html</guid>
			<description>NASA and the Worcester Polytechnic Institute (WPI) in Worcester, Mass., have opened registration and are seeking teams to compete in next year's robot technology demonstration competition, which offers as much as $1.5 million in prize money.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Oct 2012 00:00:00 EDT</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
